[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ":", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "Are they going to do that?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "going", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "LUMENTHAL: I think that the issue remains a very open -- one in the minds of many of my colleagues because they are hearing from their constituents that we really need to do something about gun violence.", "answer_tokens": ["LUMENTHAL", ":", "I", "think", "that", "the", "issue", "remains", "a", "very", "open", "--", "one", "in", "the", "minds", "of", "many", "of", "my", "colleagues", "because", "they", "are", "hearing", "from", "their", "constituents", "that", "we", "really", "need", "to", "do", "something", "about", "gun", "violence", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "Where does that leave the president?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "does", "that", "leave", "the", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "Well, the NRA never misses an opportunity to miss an opportunity.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "NRA", "never", "misses", "an", "opportunity", "to", "miss", "an", "opportunity", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "And what did you agree with him about?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "did", "you", "agree", "with", "him", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Nothing.", "answer_tokens": ["Nothing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Bill of Rights"]}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", ",", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "You don't agree with universal background checks for gun sales?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "agree", "with", "universal", "background", "checks", "for", "gun", "sales", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "In French, back to the Bill of Rights.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "French", ",", "back", "to", "the", "Bill", "of", "Rights", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "You don't agree with that?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "agree", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "Infringe on my rights.", "answer_tokens": ["Infringe", "on", "my", "rights", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "What possible infringement of your rights is it as a member of the American society if you want to buy a gun that are background checked?", "question_tokens": ["What", "possible", "infringement", "of", "your", "rights", "is", "it", "as", "a", "member", "of", "the", "American", "society", "if", "you", "want", "to", "buy", "a", "gun", "that", "are", "background", "checked", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Well, here's the deal.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "here", "'s", "the", "deal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "Would you cap ammunition magazines to a 10-round limit?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "cap", "ammunition", "magazines", "to", "a", "10-round", "limit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Because it doesn't say so in the Constitution.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "it", "does", "n't", "say", "so", "in", "the", "Constitution", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "Piers, more importantly where does it say I cannot?", "question_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "more", "importantly", "where", "does", "it", "say", "I", "can", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RBR", "RB", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "So where's the limit?", "question_tokens": ["So", "where", "'s", "the", "limit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "POS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "Well, there is not because it doesn't say it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "is", "not", "because", "it", "does", "n't", "say", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "Do you believe the Second Amendment gives you, Scottie Hughes, the right to have a tank?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "the", "Second", "Amendment", "gives", "you", ",", "Scottie", "Hughes", ",", "the", "right", "to", "have", "a", "tank", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "You know what, honestly, I don't see bullet points in the Constitution, sure.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "what", ",", "honestly", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "see", "bullet", "points", "in", "the", "Constitution", ",", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Scottie Hughes"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "Do you feel you have the right to have a tank?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "you", "have", "the", "right", "to", "have", "a", "tank", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "That's an interesting question, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "an", "interesting", "question", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "VBN", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", ":", "DT", ",", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "How can this be a sensible conversation?", "question_tokens": ["How", "can", "this", "be", "a", "sensible", "conversation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "No -- listen, listen, listen, listen -- no, listen.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "--", "listen", ",", "listen", ",", "listen", ",", "listen", "--", "no", ",", "listen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "-- say you want the right to a tank?", "question_tokens": ["--", "say", "you", "want", "the", "right", "to", "a", "tank", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "I haven't even said anything yet.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "n't", "even", "said", "anything", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "Do you think you should have the right to have a tank under the Second Amendment?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "you", "should", "have", "the", "right", "to", "have", "a", "tank", "under", "the", "Second", "Amendment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "I think the Constitution is clear and it says that we have a right to bear arms under the definition of arms.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "Constitution", "is", "clear", "and", "it", "says", "that", "we", "have", "a", "right", "to", "bear", "arms", "under", "the", "definition", "of", "arms", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "Does that include a tank?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "include", "a", "tank", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "If that is how arms is defined, I'm going to let you draw your conclusions on that.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "that", "is", "how", "arms", "is", "defined", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "let", "you", "draw", "your", "conclusions", "on", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Dana", "Dana"]}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "So have you started using the term -- have you stopped using the term assault rifle?", "question_tokens": ["So", "have", "you", "started", "using", "the", "term", "--", "have", "you", "stopped", "using", "the", "term", "assault", "rifle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Dana, Dana, Dana -- I'll come to that in a moment.", "answer_tokens": ["Dana", ",", "Dana", ",", "Dana", "--", "I", "'ll", "come", "to", "that", "in", "a", "moment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "The Second Amendment gives you, as Scottie believes, the right to have a tank?", "question_tokens": ["The", "Second", "Amendment", "gives", "you", ",", "as", "Scottie", "believes", ",", "the", "right", "to", "have", "a", "tank", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "I believe that the Second Amendment gives us all the right to bear arms.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "believe", "that", "the", "Second", "Amendment", "gives", "us", "all", "the", "right", "to", "bear", "arms", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Scottie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WRB", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "Does that include a tank?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "include", "a", "tank", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "If that's how -- if it falls under the definition of firearms.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "that", "'s", "how", "--", "if", "it", "falls", "under", "the", "definition", "of", "firearms", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "Do you think it does?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "does", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "I -- if it falls under the definition of firearms.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "if", "it", "falls", "under", "the", "definition", "of", "firearms", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "Do you think it does, Dana?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "does", ",", "Dana", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "If I say so, you're going to -- you're going to fire back.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "I", "say", "so", ",", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "--", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "fire", "back", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dana"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "Do you think it does?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "does", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "And accuse me about my interpretation.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "accuse", "me", "about", "my", "interpretation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Second Amendment"]}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "Does the -- does your personal interpretation of the Second Amendment include your right to have a tank?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "the", "--", "does", "your", "personal", "interpretation", "of", "the", "Second", "Amendment", "include", "your", "right", "to", "have", "a", "tank", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", ":", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "My personal interpretation of the Second Amendment isn't a personal interpretation.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "personal", "interpretation", "of", "the", "Second", "Amendment", "is", "n't", "a", "personal", "interpretation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "Does that include a tank?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "include", "a", "tank", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "If it falls under the definition of firearms, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "it", "falls", "under", "the", "definition", "of", "firearms", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 260, "question": "When is the last time you heard somebody want a tank and buy a tank?", "question_tokens": ["When", "is", "the", "last", "time", "you", "heard", "somebody", "want", "a", "tank", "and", "buy", "a", "tank", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Scottie has --", "answer_tokens": ["Scottie", "has", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "So you're an expert?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "'re", "an", "expert", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Well, my brother is, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "my", "brother", "is", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Columbine"]}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "You don't dispute that?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "dispute", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "And Columbine happened, and Columbine happened after that.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "Columbine", "happened", ",", "and", "Columbine", "happened", "after", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "Do you dispute that it was banned?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "dispute", "that", "it", "was", "banned", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "And Columbine happened after that.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "Columbine", "happened", "after", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "Why was it banned then under the 1994 assault weapons ban?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "was", "it", "banned", "then", "under", "the", "1994", "assault", "weapons", "ban", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Because people don't like scary-looking guns.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "people", "do", "n't", "like", "scary-looking", "guns", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1994"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dana Loesch"]}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "When is the last time you heard a crime done by one of those people?", "question_tokens": ["When", "is", "the", "last", "time", "you", "heard", "a", "crime", "done", "by", "one", "of", "those", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "OK, Dana Loesch, let's ask you that question which is about the magazine clips.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", ",", "Dana", "Loesch", ",", "let", "'s", "ask", "you", "that", "question", "which", "is", "about", "the", "magazine", "clips", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "Do you think that there is any reason why any civilian needs a magazine -- or magazine drums at it is now, over 10-round limit or more?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "there", "is", "any", "reason", "why", "any", "civilian", "needs", "a", "magazine", "--", "or", "magazine", "drums", "at", "it", "is", "now", ",", "over", "10-round", "limit", "or", "more", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "NN", ":", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "IN", "CD", "NN", "CC", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "I think that there exist reasons that exactly why we should have more than.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "there", "exist", "reasons", "that", "exactly", "why", "we", "should", "have", "more", "than", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 416, "question": "What is the point of that anecdote?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "point", "of", "that", "anecdote", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "And also, and also, Piers --", "answer_tokens": ["And", "also", ",", "and", "also", ",", "Piers", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 418, "question": "But Dana, why do you tell that story?", "question_tokens": ["But", "Dana", ",", "why", "do", "you", "tell", "that", "story", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Well, because it's to highlight that if someone has a firearm and they're able to defend themselves --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "because", "it", "'s", "to", "highlight", "that", "if", "someone", "has", "a", "firearm", "and", "they", "'re", "able", "to", "defend", "themselves", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dana"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "Have you seen the video?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "seen", "the", "video", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "Or -- I've seen -- I actually have screen shots of it.", "answer_tokens": ["Or", "--", "I", "'ve", "seen", "--", "I", "actually", "have", "screen", "shots", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "So that young man should have shot those people?", "question_tokens": ["So", "that", "young", "man", "should", "have", "shot", "those", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "I'm not saying that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "saying", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "NNS", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "RBR", "IN", "CD", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "What are you saying then?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "saying", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "There are instances where there is more than one people, more than one person coming at you.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "are", "instances", "where", "there", "is", "more", "than", "one", "people", ",", "more", "than", "one", "person", "coming", "at", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Have you ever fired one?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "fired", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "I haven't fired one.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "n't", "fired", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["15"]}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "CC", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "JJ", ":", "VBZ", ":", "NNS", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Why would anybody need that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "anybody", "need", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "Well, first and foremost, if you've never fired an AR- 15, as a woman, who also has self-defense -- has -- uses guns for self-defense and likes to know that I have that security they're a lot easier to fire than other rifles simply because of the recoil.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "and", "foremost", ",", "if", "you", "'ve", "never", "fired", "an", "AR-", "15", ",", "as", "a", "woman", ",", "who", "also", "has", "self-defense", "--", "has", "--", "uses", "guns", "for", "self-defense", "and", "likes", "to", "know", "that", "I", "have", "that", "security", "they", "'re", "a", "lot", "easier", "to", "fire", "than", "other", "rifles", "simply", "because", "of", "the", "recoil", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Or one of these high-capacity magazines?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "one", "of", "these", "high-capacity", "magazines", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Piers, how are law-abiding --", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "how", "are", "law-abiding", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["James Holmes"]}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Why should I be punished?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "should", "I", "be", "punished", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "James Holmes was a law-abiding citizen.", "answer_tokens": ["James", "Holmes", "was", "a", "law-abiding", "citizen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Scottie"]}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 565, "question": "Do you realize that there are laws that have been passed to incentivize states recording these people?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "realize", "that", "there", "are", "laws", "that", "have", "been", "passed", "to", "incentivize", "states", "recording", "these", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "Scottie said early that she --", "answer_tokens": ["Scottie", "said", "early", "that", "she", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Newtown"]}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "Is there anything there you agreed with?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "anything", "there", "you", "agreed", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "You know, I'm really -- because I think that he was moved by what happened at Newtown, which I think anybody would have been.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "really", "--", "because", "I", "think", "that", "he", "was", "moved", "by", "what", "happened", "at", "Newtown", ",", "which", "I", "think", "anybody", "would", "have", "been", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "Was there anything you agreed within the president's proposals?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "there", "anything", "you", "agreed", "within", "the", "president", "'s", "proposals", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Georgia"]}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "You know something?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "something", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "-- I would have liked to have the mother from Georgia that sat there.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "I", "would", "have", "liked", "to", "have", "the", "mother", "from", "Georgia", "that", "sat", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate", "House"]}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "How can he do it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "can", "he", "do", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "Well, he has this stuff he chose precisely because he doesn't have to send it through the Senate or the House.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "has", "this", "stuff", "he", "chose", "precisely", "because", "he", "does", "n't", "have", "to", "send", "it", "through", "the", "Senate", "or", "the", "House", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "Well, what the bloody hell are they?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "the", "bloody", "hell", "are", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "I grew up on a farm in a world surrounded by guns.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "grew", "up", "on", "a", "farm", "in", "a", "world", "surrounded", "by", "guns", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 661, "question": "What are you left with?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "left", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "Well, it's fun.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "fun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 664, "question": "Is fun a good enough excuse?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "fun", "a", "good", "enough", "excuse", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 665, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "We know that three Americans may be among the hostages, I think?", "question_tokens": ["We", "know", "that", "three", "Americans", "may", "be", "among", "the", "hostages", ",", "I", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "We know very little about this.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "know", "very", "little", "about", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 700, "question": "How are you doing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 701, "answer": "I'm good.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 702, "question": "Thank you How are you?", "question_tokens": ["Thank", "you", "How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 703, "answer": "I'm feeling great.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "feeling", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 709, "question": "What is your take on what was a very momentous day today for President Obama and his administration, and I think for America?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "take", "on", "what", "was", "a", "very", "momentous", "day", "today", "for", "President", "Obama", "and", "his", "administration", ",", "and", "I", "think", "for", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 710, "answer": "Well, look, I think this is a really polarizing issue.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "look", ",", "I", "think", "this", "is", "a", "really", "polarizing", "issue", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"], "PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", ":", "WRB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 718, "question": "Do you believe the Constitution gives you the right to have a tank?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "the", "Constitution", "gives", "you", "the", "right", "to", "have", "a", "tank", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 719, "answer": "Well, I think the Constitution -- when the Founding Fathers wrote the Constitution, I don't think they envisioned, you know, rapid-fire weapons or anything like that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "Constitution", "--", "when", "the", "Founding", "Fathers", "wrote", "the", "Constitution", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "they", "envisioned", ",", "you", "know", ",", "rapid-fire", "weapons", "or", "anything", "like", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBP", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 724, "question": "They couldn't find any common ground in anything?", "question_tokens": ["They", "could", "n't", "find", "any", "common", "ground", "in", "anything", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 725, "answer": "But those are just two people.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "those", "are", "just", "two", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "PRP", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 738, "question": "Did you get to know him?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "get", "to", "know", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 739, "answer": "He basically, you know, asked me what the weather was going to be, and then kept moving.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "basically", ",", "you", "know", ",", "asked", "me", "what", "the", "weather", "was", "going", "to", "be", ",", "and", "then", "kept", "moving", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 744, "question": "What do you think of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 745, "answer": "Well, look --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "look", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 818, "question": "Do you feel like it's got you all energized again?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "like", "it", "'s", "got", "you", "all", "energized", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 819, "answer": "I think, look, we were always energized.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", ",", "look", ",", "we", "were", "always", "energized", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 850, "question": "Your neck is disappearing, like the rest of you, at a rate -- you've lost an unfeasible amount of wait, 350 pounds down to -- fighting wait now?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "neck", "is", "disappearing", ",", "like", "the", "rest", "of", "you", ",", "at", "a", "rate", "--", "you", "'ve", "lost", "an", "unfeasible", "amount", "of", "wait", ",", "350", "pounds", "down", "to", "--", "fighting", "wait", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "TO", ":", "VBG", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 851, "answer": "Right, 205.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", ",", "205", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 877, "question": "Because you can have all the diets and things in the world, but until your head's right -- what are the things that you felt were most effective?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "you", "can", "have", "all", "the", "diets", "and", "things", "in", "the", "world", ",", "but", "until", "your", "head", "'s", "right", "--", "what", "are", "the", "things", "that", "you", "felt", "were", "most", "effective", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PDT", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", ":", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "JJS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 878, "answer": "A, in this country, we need to cut back on portions.", "answer_tokens": ["A", ",", "in", "this", "country", ",", "we", "need", "to", "cut", "back", "on", "portions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 905, "question": "Have you ever seen a happy runner?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "seen", "a", "happy", "runner", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 906, "answer": "Let me tell you about a high work out.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "tell", "you", "about", "a", "high", "work", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "EX", "VBZ", "JJR", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 921, "question": "The White House incident, probably the most revolting story I've ever heard on national television?", "question_tokens": ["The", "White", "House", "incident", ",", "probably", "the", "most", "revolting", "story", "I", "'ve", "ever", "heard", "on", "national", "television", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 922, "answer": "I am sure there is worse, but here is the deal.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "sure", "there", "is", "worse", ",", "but", "here", "is", "the", "deal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 942, "question": "Can we have you read the tease to the break, please?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "we", "have", "you", "read", "the", "tease", "to", "the", "break", ",", "please", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 943, "answer": "All right.", "answer_tokens": ["All", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 953, "question": "In one word, what will the weather be like tomorrow?", "question_tokens": ["In", "one", "word", ",", "what", "will", "the", "weather", "be", "like", "tomorrow", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "DT", "NN", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 954, "answer": "It's going to be spectacular.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "spectacular", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]